This series is made for entertainment purpose only. The characters, actions and places are fictional. There is no intention to disrespect any authority, profession or community. Viewer discretion is advised.
Esta série é feita apenas para fins de entretenimento. As personagens, ações e lugares são fictícios. Não há qualquer intenção de desrespeitar qualquer autoridade, profissão ou comunidade. Recomenda-se a discrição do espectador.
Wit.
Sagacidade.
He is Rin’s boyfriend,
É o namorado da Rin,
Narong’s sister who committed suicide.
Irmã de Narong que se suicidou.
Stop!
Parar!
The laws that you respect and look up to...
As leis que respeita e admira...
can never keep those bastards behind bars for long.
nunca conseguiremos manter estes sacanas atrás das grades por muito tempo.
Songyod is arrested.
Songyod é preso.
I tried to ask Narong about the thing that happened in the cellar today.
Tentei perguntar ao Narong sobre o que aconteceu na cave hoje.
It seems he had no idea what was happening to him.
Parece que não fazia ideia do que se estava a passar com ele.
Is there anyone who can tell us about what we saw?
Alguém nos pode contar o que vimos?
You should know where you stand and better stay by his side as a big brother.
Deve saber onde está e é melhor ficar ao lado dele como um irmão mais velho.
I’ll try to keep that in mind.
Tentarei ter isso em mente.
Until your time is done.
Até que o seu tempo acabe.
Phaya.
Lá.
Billy – Patchanon Ounsa-ard
Billy – Patchanon Ounsa-ard
Babe - Tanatat Phanviriyakool
Babe - Tanatat Phanviriyakool
Tack – Phongsakorn Sukeing
Obrigado – Phongsakorn Sukeing
Poom – Nuttapart Tuntistianchai
Poom – Nuttapart Tuntistianchai
Heng – Asavarid pinitkanchanapan Surprise – Pitikorn Siripornsawan Gap – Jakarin Puribhat
Heng – Asavarid pinitkanchanapan Surpresa – Pitikorn Siripornsawan Gap – Jakarin Puribhat
Akk – Akarat Nimitchai
Akk – Akarat Nimitchai
Guests Yo - Tassawan Saeneewong Koi - Tarika Tidatith
Convidados Yo - Tassawan Saeneewong Koi - Tarika Tidatith
Guests Wit – Phutharit Prombandal Nat - Nat Sakdatorn Thakrit Chaiwut
Convidados com – Phutharit Prombandal Nat - Nat Sakdatorn Thakrit Chaiwut
Guests Freen – Sarocha chankimha Nam – Orntara Poonsak
Convidados Freen – Sarocha chankimha Nam – Orntara Poonsak
Guests Ice - Athichanan Srisevok Pun – Thanapol Peechapat
Convidados Gelo - Athichana Srisevok Pun - Thanapol Peechapat
Guests Tae - Nanthasai Visalyaputra Kaona – Kittipat Kaewcharoen Yoshi – Rinrada Thurapan
Convidados Tae - Nanthasai Visalyaputra Kaona – Kittipat Kaewcharoen Yoshi – Rinrada Thurapan
Guests Young Phaya: Techin Na wong Young Tharn: Rachan Madsee Young Yai: Supakorn Kantanit
Convidados Young Phaya: Techin Na wong Young Tharn: Rachan Madsee Young Yai: Supakorn Kantanit
Introducing Songjed – Sarochinee Pethampai Pear – Neilinyah Taweearayapat
Featuring Songjed – Sarochinee Pethampai Pear – Neilinyah Taweearayapat
Introducing Fay – Kunyaphat Na nakorn May – Yada Watcharamusik
Com Fay – Kunyaphat Na nakorn May – Yada Watcharamusik
Directed by Nattapong Wongkaweepairoj
Realizado porNattapong Wongkaweepairoj
The Sign
O Sinal
We finally meet again.
Finalmente encontrámo-nos novamente.
Who are you?
Quem és tu?
Why are you always in my dream?
Porque é que estás sempre nos meus sonhos?
Don’t you remember me?
Não se lembra de mim?
Use your heart instead of your eyes.
Use o seu coração em vez dos seus olhos.
And you’ll finally see.
E você finalmente verá.
Phaya.
Lá.
Phaya, are you okay?
Phaya, estás bem?
I’ve been calling for ages.
Estou a ligar há séculos.
Grandma said dinner is ready.
A avó disse que o jantar está pronto.
If you don’t want her to get even more upset, you better hurry up and come down.
Se não quer que ela fique ainda mais perturbada, é melhor apressar-se e descer.
Okay, I’ll be right behind you.
Certo, estarei logo atrás de ti.
Tharn.
Tharn.
Yes?
Sim?
Where are you?
Onde estás?
Swimming at my condo.
Nadar no meu apartamento.
With whom?
Com quem?
Khem and Thongthai. Yai is on the way.
Khem e Thongthai. Yai está a caminho.
What’s the matter?
Qual é o problema?
I had a bad dream about you so I was just worried.
Tive um pesadelo contigo, por isso fiquei preocupado.
Don’t worry. I can take care of myself.
Não se preocupe. Sei cuidar de mim.
But I’m really worried this time.
Mas desta vez estou realmente preocupado.
Maybe you should take some days off for a while.
Talvez devesse tirar alguns dias de férias durante algum tempo.
Think of it as a rehab for your injury.
Pense nisto como uma reabilitação para a sua lesão.
You can get back to work once you’re fully recovered.
Poderá voltar ao trabalho quando estiver totalmente recuperado.
Are you saying that I should tell the Inspector...
Está a dizer que eu deveria contar ao Inspetor...
that I need to take leave because of your bad dream?
que preciso de tirar uma folga por causa do seu pesadelo?
Are you nuts?
Você é louco?
Tharn.
Tharn.
This is not different from when I doubted about your vision.
Isto não é diferente de quando duvidei da sua visão.
But right now I won’t deny what you are seeing.
Mas agora não vou negar o que está a ver.
Yes, it might be just a dream.
Sim, pode ser apenas um sonho.
But the fact that I keep dreaming about it again and again...
Mas o facto de continuar a sonhar com isso repetidamente...
and you are always in those dreams,
e você está sempre nesses sonhos,
don’t you think it’s actually the same as your vision?
não acha que é realmente a mesma coisa que a sua visão?
You don’t need to worry about me.
Não precisa de se preocupar comigo.
I’ll take a good care of myself, okay?
Vou cuidar bem de mim, ok?
Bye.
Adeus.
Wait. Tharn! Tharn!
Espere. Tharn! Tharn!
Hey, where are you going? Grandma will bite your head off if you leave now.
Ei, onde vais? A avó vai arrancar-lhe a cabeça se for embora agora.
I have something urgent to take care of.
Tenho algo urgente para resolver.
Hang on. You’re acting weird.
Espere aí. Está a agir de forma estranha.
Is it about someone? Who is it?
É sobre alguém? Quem é?
Just a friend.
Apenas um amigo.
- My colleague. - Hmmmm
- O meu colega. - Hmmmm
He probably needs my help with his work.
Provavelmente precisa da minha ajuda com o seu trabalho.
Are you sure he’s just a friend?
Tem a certeza de que ele é apenas um amigo?
Why do you have to rush out like this? Why can’t you just give him a call?
Porque é que tem de sair a correr assim? Porque não liga para ele?
I already did but he didn’t pick up.
Eu já fiz isso, mas ele não atendeu.
- Why are you being so nosy, cheeky monkey? - Ouch!
- Porque é que estás a ser tão intrometido, seu macaco atrevido? - Ai!
I’m leaving.
Vou embora.
Hello, Phaya.
Olá.
And this is...
E isto é...
This is Nee, my little sister. Do you remember her?
Esta é a Nee, a minha irmãzinha. Lembra-se dela?
I see...
Eu vejo...
I haven’t seen you for a while. You’ve grown into a beauty.
Há tempo que não te vejo. Ficaste uma beleza.
Hello, Dao.
Olá, Dao.
Oh, you’re here? That was quick.
Ah, chegou? Esta foi rápida.
Hello, Grandma.
Olá avó.
I can’t believe someone like Phaya...
Não acredito que alguém como a Phaya...
would be so superstitious about his bad dream like this.
seria tão supersticioso sobre o seu pesadelo assim.
Hey, are you and Phaya together?
Ei, tu e a Phaya estão juntos?
What?
O quê?
Of course, not.
Claro que não.
Well, he seems to worry about you a lot.
Bem, ele parece preocupar-se muito consigo.
Probably a lot more than just a colleague would do.
Provavelmente muito mais do que apenas um colega faria.
He was having a bad dream about you and it worries him to death.
Ele estava a ter um pesadelo consigo e isso preocupava-o muito.
I’m sure the power of love he has for you is very immense, my bro.
Tenho a certeza que o poder do amor que ele tem por ti é imenso, meu irmão.
Shut up, you jerk.
Cale-se, seu idiota.
Listen.
Escutar.
Phaya and I are just colleagues. That’s it.
A Phaya e eu somos apenas colegas. Só isso.
If you don’t like him that way...
Se não gosta dele assim...
why do you always have to protect him?
Porque é que tem sempre que protegê-lo?
You even took the stab for him.
Até levou a facada por ele.
Before you’d say anyting,
Antes que diga qualquer coisa,
I want to use your heart rather than your head.
Quero usar o seu coração e não a sua cabeça.
Awww….
Awww….
Stop. I already told you guys and we are just friends.
Parem. Já vos disse e somos apenas amigos.
- Swear? / - Would you swear?
- Jurar? / - Juraria?
- Go on. Swear it. - Would you swear?
- Vá em frente. Jure. - Você juraria?
What?
O quê?
I’d rather not.
Prefiro não.
What if Phaya likes you then? What would you say?
E se a Phaya gostar de si? O que diria?
Yeah, what would you do?
Sim, o que faria?
Will you give him a chance?
Dar-lhe-á uma chance?
Come on, say it.
Vamos lá, diga.
I think you’re imagining things.
Acho que está a imaginar coisas.
The way Phaya behaves when he’s around you…
A forma como a Phaya se comporta quando está perto de si…
I used to be like that too.
Eu também costumava ser assim.
Geez, what’s wrong with you?
Ena, o que há de errado consigo?
For Baby and I,
Para o bebé e para mim,
our relationship also started from me always caring for him.
a nossa relação também começou porque eu sempre me importei com ele.
Geez, stop it. It wasn’t an act of caring at all.
Ui, pare com isso. Não foi um ato de carinho.
It actually started with a chaos.
Na verdade, tudo começou com um caos.
The first time I saw you,
A primeira vez que te vi,
I almost wanted to quit the university.
Quase quis abandonar a universidade.
What happened?
O que aconteceu?
Tell us then. I really want to know.
Então, conte-nos. Quero muito saber.
Well, our relationship began to bloom...
Bem, a nossa relação começou a florescer...
on the day when our young hearts were still yearning for love.
no dia em que os nossos jovens corações ainda ansiavam por amor.
With my bicep muscle under the warm sunlight.
Com o meu bíceps sob a luz quente do sol.
It was the beauty of my young and muscular body…
Era a beleza do meu corpo jovem e musculado…
that made him fallen for me.
que fez com que se apaixonasse por mim.
You have a pose as well.
Também tem uma pose.
Can you get to the point now? I’m listening.
Pode ir direto ao ponto agora? Estou a ouvir.
Well, it all started like this…
Bem, tudo começou assim…
[A university in the north]
[Uma universidade no norte]
[2009]
[2009]
(Screaming)
(Gritando)
Definitely me.
Definitivamente eu.
Shit!
Merda!
Is there anyone?
Tem alguém?
Hey, are you done? Do you need a hand?
Ei, já terminou? Precisa de ajuda?
Wow, they look cute on you.
Uau, ficam-te fofos.
I’ll wash them and return them to you later.
Vou lavá-los e devolvê-los mais tarde.
No worry. I’ll take care of your wet clothes too.
Não se preocupe. Eu também trato das suas roupas molhadas.
Think of it as my apology.
Pense nisso como um pedido de desculpas.
I’m leaving then.
Então vou embora.
Hey, wait.
Ei, espere.
I have a question.
Eu tenho uma pergunta.
Do you believe infinity?
Acredita no infinito?
What?
O quê?
Infinity. Isn’t that what you call something like fate?
Infinito. Não é assim que se chama a algo como destino?
You know?
Sabes?
That’s ‘Destiny’.
Isto é "Destino".
Huh?
Hã?
Look at my lips.
Olhe para os meus lábios.
- Des... / - Des...
- Alguns... / - Alguns...
- Ti... / - Ti...
- Tu... / - Tu...
- Ny. / - Ny.
- Sra. / - Sra.
- Destiny. - Tishni.
- Destino. - Dente.
No. DESTINY.
Não. DESTINO.
Tishni
Dente
Stop it.
Pare com isso.
Then what does that sentence I just said mean?
Então o que significa aquela frase que acabei de dizer?
How can you not know the meaning of what you said?
Como pode não saber o significado do que disse?
It means whether or not you believe that destiny exists.
Significa se acredita ou não que o destino existe.
I see.
Eu vejo.
Actually, I know what it means. I just want you to ask me the same thing too
Na verdade, sei o que isso significa. Só quero que me pergunte a mesma coisa também.
But if you ask me, I do.
Mas se me perguntar, eu sei.
Because it was my bicep muscle under the warm sunlight…
Porque era o meu músculo bíceps sob a luz quente do sol…
and the beauty of my young and muscular body, that have brought us together.
e a beleza do meu corpo jovem e musculado, que nos unia.
Wow, that sounds so romantic. I’m so good at it.
Uau, isso parece tão romântico. Sou muito boa nisso.
Well done to myself.
Parabéns a mim.
Don’t you find it romantic?
Não acha isso romântico?
Please excuse me.
Por favor, com licença.
- See you. / - Bye.
- Até à próxima. / - Adeus.
Oh, wow.
Uau!
Romantic , wasn’t it?
Romântico, não é?
So cheeky.
Tão atrevido.
I thought I was watching ‘Secret Crush On You The Series’.
Pensei que estava a ver a série "Secret Crush On You".
You two seem to get off on the wrong foot.
Vocês os dois parecem ter começado com o pé esquerdo.
How come you ended up dating each other?
Como é que acabaram por namorar?
Well, after that day...
Bem, depois desse dia...
I kept following him to offer my sincere apology.
Continuei a segui-lo para apresentar as minhas sinceras desculpas.
But the more time I spent with him, the more I started to have feelings for him.
Mas quanto mais tempo passava com ele, mais sentimentos começava a ter por ele.
So I decided to go after him.
Então decidi ir atrás dele.
Hi, baby.
Oi, bebé.
Are you...?
Estás...?
Yes. I mean you, baby.
Sim. Estou a falar de ti, querido.
Here you go.
Aqui vai.
I already washed them. They smell so nice.
Já os lavei. Estão com um cheiro tão bom.
If you don’t believe me, then I’ll show you.
Se não acredita em mim, então vou mostrar-lhe.
You idiot! That’s my underpants. Why did you smell it?
Seu idiota! Esta é a minha calcinha. Por que razão sentiu o cheiro?
What is it?
O que é?
Your clothes. Please take them back.
As suas roupas. Por favor, leve-as de volta.
I’d be going then.
Eu iria então.
Wait.
Espera.
Let’s find something to eat. It’s on me.
Vamos procurar algo para comer. É por minha conta.
When will you stop bothering me?
Quando é que vai parar de me incomodar?
How can I do that? We’re not even together yet.
Como posso fazer isso? Ainda nem sequer estamos juntos.
I’m sorry but I don’t like men.
Lamento, mas não gosto de homens.
Why don’t you go after those junior girls who admire you?
Why don’t you go after those junior girls who admire you?
Hey, wait.
Ei, espere.
I just want to know you as a friend.
I just want to know you as a friend.
I already sent you an invitation. Will you accept it?
I already sent you an invitation. Will you accept it?
If not, you’d be so rude though.
If not, you’d be so rude though.
Judging from your look,
Judging from your look,
you seem to be quite educated.
you seem to be quite educated.
So, I guess you won’t be so rude to me.
So, I guess you won’t be so rude to me.
Do you really want to get to know me that much?
Do you really want to get to know me that much?
Why don’t you give me a chance to get to know you?
Why don’t you give me a chance to get to know you?
Maybe, if you do...
Maybe, if you do...
and we have some time to get to know each other,
and we have some time to get to know each other,
you and I might turn out to be a perfect match.
you and I might turn out to be a perfect match.
As friends, I mean.
As friends, I mean.
Or maybe when we get to know each other more,
Or maybe when we get to know each other more,
you might fall head over heels for me.
you might fall head over heels for me.
Why are you being so persistent?
Why are you being so persistent?
Because I am Khem.
Because I am Khem.
I’m Thongthai.
I’m Thongthai.
Woo-hoo!
Woo-hoo!
What are you doing?
O que estás a fazer?
I don’t like wasting time. Can we skip some steps?
I don’t like wasting time. Can we skip some steps?
We’re now close.
We’re now close.
Let’s go find something to eat.
Let’s go find something to eat.
Tonight, I’m going to make you get to know me even more.
Tonight, I’m going to make you get to know me even more.
Every part of me.
Every part of me.
Okay. But let me warn you that my standard is pretty high.
Okay. But let me warn you that my standard is pretty high.
If it turns out to be below my standard, you have to leave me alone.
If it turns out to be below my standard, you have to leave me alone.
Well, if you say so.
Well, if you say so.
You got it.
You got it.
How was it, baby? Sexy?
How was it, baby? Sexy?
Respect, respect, respect.
Respect, respect, respect.
So, you guys just skipped the talk and went straight to sex.
So, you guys just skipped the talk and went straight to sex.
Why so hurry?
Why so hurry?
Well, if we’re going ot be in a relationship,
Well, if we’re going ot be in a relationship,
we’d have a lot more time to talk later on anyway.
we’d have a lot more time to talk later on anyway.
I’d rather do that thing first.
I’d rather do that thing first.
So that I’d know if we both are on the same page. I don’t want to waste time.
So that I’d know if we both are on the same page. I don’t want to waste time.
By the way,
Já agora,
I won’t mind if you’d also adopt my method.
I won’t mind if you’d also adopt my method.
You’ll find out right the way...
You’ll find out right the way...
whether you two are made for each other or not.
whether you two are made for each other or not.
I don’t need to do that.
I don’t need to do that.
Because I still insist that I don’t like Phaya that way.
Because I still insist that I don’t like Phaya that way.
Awww, he’s stubborn.
Awww, he’s stubborn.
He just ran.
He just ran.
Or maybe he probably meant it, that he doesn’t really have feelings for Phaya.
Or maybe he probably meant it, that he doesn’t really have feelings for Phaya.
He might already like someone else.
He might already like someone else.
Is it me?
Is it me?
Obviously not.
Obviously not.
That was hard.
That was hard.
Let’s brainstorm.
Let’s brainstorm.
We hardly have any case to work on these days.
We hardly have any case to work on these days.
Yeah.
Sim.
Let’s find some time and go on a trip together.
Let’s find some time and go on a trip together.
Maybe it would help Tharn and Phaya...
Maybe it would help Tharn and Phaya...
to get closer to each other when they are both naked.
to get closer to each other when they are both naked.
Eat this! So that you can keep your mouth shut.
Eat this! So that you can keep your mouth shut.
Geez! What the fuck!
Geez! What the fuck!
Damn you.
Maldito.
Yai.
Sim.
Has Tharn ever have a boyfriend or girlfriend before?
Has Tharn ever have a boyfriend or girlfriend before?
Yes, but that person was dead.
Yes, but that person was dead.
- Dead? / - Yes
- Dead? / - Yes
So, he’s afraid. He doesn’t want to get hurt like that again.
So, he’s afraid. He doesn’t want to get hurt like that again.
These fruits are fresh from the market.
These fruits are fresh from the market.
My aunt asked me to send her best regards to you.
My aunt asked me to send her best regards to you.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
- That one is for Phaya. - Thanks a lot.
- That one is for Phaya. - Thanks a lot.
Phaya is injured from work again.
Phaya is injured from work again.
So, my aunt told me to pay a visit as soon as I can.
So, my aunt told me to pay a visit as soon as I can.
It seems like you had already known beforehand that he’d be injured.
It seems like you had already known beforehand that he’d be injured.
Well, that day when I went to see him at the unit,
Well, that day when I went to see him at the unit,
I remember he was also injured from work.
I remember he was also injured from work.
I had a hunch that someone hot-tempered like him would eventually get himself injured again.
I had a hunch that someone hot-tempered like him would eventually get himself injured again.
Well, I’m fine now.
Well, I’m fine now.
That’s why I didn’t tell you. I don’t want to bother you or anyone else.
That’s why I didn’t tell you. I don’t want to bother you or anyone else.
Whether it’s a big or small injury, our parents will always be worried about us.
Whether it’s a big or small injury, our parents will always be worried about us.
Grandma, I think we should ask him to quit being a cop.
Grandma, I think we should ask him to quit being a cop.
He has just started working and look how often he got injured.
Começou a trabalhar há pouco e veja quantas vezes se lesionou.
I’m afraid I won’t be able to stop him since it’s the job that he likes.
Receio não conseguir impedi-lo, pois é o trabalho que ele gosta.
I don’t like to force anyone to do something against his will.
Não gosto de obrigar ninguém a fazer algo contra a sua vontade.
He’s free to do whatever he loves...
Ele é livre para fazer o que ama...
as long as it’s not so dangerous that he has to risk his life for it.
desde que não seja tão perigoso que ele tenha de arriscar a vida por isso.
I totally agree with you.
Concordo plenamente consigo.
You can do any job you like.
Pode fazer qualquer trabalho que quiser.
But you must also have a work-life balance.
Mas também é preciso ter equilíbrio entre a vida pessoal e profissional.
Don’t devote yourself to work so much that you forget to care about those around you, or someone close to you.
Não se dedique tanto ao trabalho ao ponto de se esquecer de se preocupar com as pessoas que o rodeiam ou com alguém próximo.
Do you agree?
Você concorda?
If you really love your job as a police officer, maybe you should find someone to take care of you.
Se realmente adora o seu trabalho como polícia, talvez devesse encontrar alguém para cuidar de si.
So that he or she can look after you when you get injured again.
Para que ele ou ela possa cuidar de si quando se magoar novamente.
Well, he has both Grandma and I to look after him.
Bem, ele tem a avó e eu para cuidar dele.
So, you don’t have to worry about that.
Assim, não precisa de se preocupar com isso.
Nee, listen to me.
Nee, ouve-me.
You also need to live your own life.
Também precisa de viver a sua própria vida.
You can’t spend your whole life looking after your big brother.
Não pode passar a vida inteira a cuidar do seu irmão mais velho.
Unless you don’t want to have anyone.
A não ser que não queira ter ninguém.
Please excuse me for being rude.
Por favor, desculpe-me por ser rude.
But I was wondering if you’re already taken?
Mas queria saber se já tem algum compromisso?
Well...
Bem...
Taken? A naughty girl like her?
Comprometida? Uma miúda safada como ela?
Obviously, not.
Obviamente que não.
Thank you so much for your concern about me though.
Muito obrigado pela sua preocupação comigo.
All right then. Let’s start eating. We’ve been chatting for quite some time.
Tudo bem, então. Vamos começar a comer. Estamos a falar há algum tempo.
Okay.
Ok.
Eat this too, Grandma.
Coma isso também, avó.
You should eat more so that you’d get better soon.
Devia comer mais para melhorar logo.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
You should eat more too.
Também deveria comer mais.
You probably didn’t get to eat Thai food that often when you were abroad.
Provavelmente não comeu comida tailandesa com tanta frequência quando estava no estrangeiro.
Oh, but I actually did. I worked part-time at a Thai restuarant.
Ah, mas eu fiz mesmo isso. Trabalhei em part-time num restaurante tailandês.
Grandma.
Avó.
My aunt told me that you will also attend the art exhibition. Is that right?
A minha tia contou-me que também vais à exposição de arte. É isso mesmo?
Yes. Your aunt called and invited me by herself.
Sim. A tia dele ligou e convidou-me pessoalmente.
Will Phaya be there too?
A Phaya também estará lá?
My aunt said you’ll also take him with you.
A minha tia disse que também o levará consigo.
Ah, that’s right.
Ah, é isso mesmo.
Can you please come with me? My friends really want to see you.
Podes vir comigo, por favor? Os meus amigos querem muito ver-te.
You hardly go anywhere with me these days.
Ultimamente quase não sais comigo para lado nenhum.
All you do is work.
Tudo o que faz é trabalhar.
Well...I...
Bem... eu...
Of course, Grandma. I’ll go with you.
Claro, avó. Eu vou contigo.
I’m also free.
Eu também estou livre.
Can I go too?
Posso ir também?
Of course.
Claro.
Can’t he just at least send me a sticker?
Ele não pode pelo menos enviar-me um autocolante?
(Door scratching)
(Arranhão na porta)
Nee?
Não é?
What’s the matter?
Qual é o problema?
I bring you some fruits that Dao gave us.
Trago-lhes alguns frutos que o Dao nos deu.
Hmm, are you really my sister?
Hmm, és mesmo minha irmã?
Why are you so kind today?
Porque está tão gentil hoje?
This is all you’d get to eat. The rest is mine.
É tudo o que come. O resto é meu.
Thanks a lot. Put it over there. I’ll eat them soon.
Muito obrigado. Pode deixar aqui. Vou comer já.
Aren’t you done? Go back to your room then.
Ainda não terminou? Depois volte para o seu quarto.
I’m not in a hurry.
Não tenho pressa.
Your room looks so comfy today.
O seu quarto parece tão confortável hoje.
What?
O quê?
Eat this first.
Coma isto primeiro.
Eat it.
Coma.
What is it?
O que é?
I’ll get to the point then.
Assim irei direto ao ponto.
Okay.
Ok.
How close were you and Dao when you two were studying abroad?
Quão próximos eram você e o Dao quando ambos estudavam no estrangeiro?
Grandma asked me to take care of her because she’s the favourite niece of her best friend. That’s all.
A avó pediu-me para cuidar dela porque é a sobrinha favorita da sua melhor amiga. Só isso.
Have you and Dao ever been together?
Você e o Dao já estiveram juntos?
You are quite a player. So, I think it’s possible.
É um ótimo jogador. Portanto, acho que é possível.
- Geez, you monkey. / - Ouch.
- Ena, seu macaco. / - Ai.
That’s enough.
Já chega.
Just answer my question so that I can be at ease.
Basta responder à minha pergunta para que eu possa ficar descansado.
No, Dao and I are like brother and sister.
Não, o Dao e eu somos como irmão e irmã.
Okay, I feel better now.
Ok, já me sinto melhor.
What’s wrong with you, Miss Paranee?
O que se passa consigo, Srta. Paranee?
Why are you so interested in Dao?
Porque está tão interessado no Dao?
Well, she is beautiful and seems to know you well.
Bem, ela é linda e parece conhecer-te bem.
Our Grandma seems to like her a lot too.
Parece que a nossa avó também gosta muito dela.
So, I just want to know more about her.
Então, só quero saber mais sobre ela.
That’s all.
Isso é tudo.
She and you would probably make a perfect couple though.
Ela e você provavelmente formariam um casal perfeito.
I mean, consdisering all other factors.
Quer dizer, considerando todos os outros fatores.
She’s actually too good for someone like you.
Na verdade, ela é demasiado boa para alguém como tu.
But good enough for you, right?
Mas bom o suficiente para si, certo?
What?
O quê?
Don’t try to be a shipper.
Não tente ser um remetente.
I’m leaving.
Vou embora.
You’re changing the subject.
Está a mudar de assunto.
Namami. Where’s Namami?
Namami. Onde está a Namami?
Where’d he go?
Para onde foi ele?
Who’s this girl?
Quem é esta menina?
And this guy too.
E este gajo também.
Hmm, that girl is the one I often dream of.
Hmm, esta rapariga é aquela com quem eu sempre sonho.
That guy is my colleague.
Aquele tipo é meu colega.
Ahh, is he the one you were rushing out to see this evening?
Ah, é ele que estava a correr para ver esta noite?
Yeah.
Sim.
I just feel that these two have something in common.
Simplesmente sinto que estes dois têm algo em comum.
Huh? But this girl is just someone from your dream.
Hã? Mas esta rapariga é apenas alguém dos seus sonhos.
That’s right.
Isso mesmo.
Hang on. Are you saying that you’re worried about your colleague whose name is Tharn?
Espere aí. Está a dizer que está preocupado com o seu colega chamado Tharn?
So much that you try to relate him with a girl you often see in your dream?
Tanto que tenta relacioná-lo com uma rapariga que vê frequentemente nos seus sonhos?
Is this the answer you’ve always been looking for?
É esta a resposta que sempre procurou?
To find out who or what it is that you saw when you were drowning.
Para descobrir quem ou o que viu quando estava a afogar-se.
Nee.
Não.
Is your friend, Wi, still teaching at the Faculty of Archaeology?
O seu amigo, Wi, ainda leciona na Faculdade de Arqueologia?
The one you used to say she was cute?
Aquela que costumava dizer que era gira?
Yeah.
Sim.
When we last talked, she said she would quit to open an art gallery.
Quando falámos pela última vez, ela disse que ia parar para abrir uma galeria de arte.
Why?
Porquê?
Are you sure?
Tem a certeza?
Yes, I am. My gallery has never bought or displayed this kind of art.
Sim, sou. A minha galeria nunca comprou ou expôs este tipo de arte.
But I was told that it was sold here.
Mas disseram-me que era vendido aqui.
I’d still insist that my gallery has never bought that kind of art.
Eu ainda insistiria que a minha galeria nunca comprou este tipo de arte.
You can search the gallery if you want to.
Pode pesquisar na galeria se quiser.
You’re not lying to me, aren’t you?
Não me está a mentir, está?
No, I’m not lying.
Não, não estou a mentir.
Hey.
Olá.
Phaya.
Lá.
Wi.
Wi.
How are you doing?
Como estás?
I’m good.
Estou bem.
Long time no see.
Há quanto tempo.
It’s been over a year, I think.
Penso que já passou mais de um ano.
I’m sorry for a sudden visit. I also come empty-handed.
Peço desculpa pela visita repentina. Eu também vim de mãos vazias.
By the way, that man looks very suspicious.
Aliás, aquele homem parece muito suspeito.
He’s looking for his artwork.
Ele está à procura da sua obra de arte.
He said his girlfriend sold it to my gallery.
Disse que a namorada vendeu para a minha galeria.
But I’ve never bought any artwork from his girlfriend.
Mas nunca comprei nenhuma obra de arte da namorada dele.
This happens a lot in the art industry.
Isso acontece muito na indústria da arte.
Stealing someone else’s works and sell them.
Roubar obras a outra pessoa e vendê-las.
Some are rare antiques which the owners have no idea how valuable they are.
Algumas são antiguidades raras cujos proprietários não fazem ideia do seu valor.
Those with a keen eye would buy them and resell at a much higher price.
Aqueles com um olhar atento comprá-los-iam e revenderiam por um preço muito mais elevado.
When the owners of the work found out, they often came out to claim their rights of ownership.
Quando os donos da obra descobriam, muitas vezes saíam para reivindicar os seus direitos de propriedade.
But some of them are forged. They are fake ones.
Mas algumas delas são falsificadas. São falsas.
You can hardly tell them apart from the original works though.
Mas é difícil distingui-los das obras originais.
It sounds quite complicated but I got it somehow.
Parece bastante complicado, mas de alguma forma consegui.
There’s always a story hidden behind each artwork.
Há sempre uma história escondida por detrás de cada obra de arte.
Each has its own unique value, method, and expertise...
Cada um tem o seu próprio valor, método e especialização...
depending on the artist who has created that piece of work.
dependendo do artista que criou aquela obra.
Those are what make the artwork valuable.
É isso que torna a obra de arte valiosa.
Is this why you decided to quit teaching at the university and open an art gallery instead?
Foi por isso que decidiu deixar de dar aulas na universidade e abrir uma galeria de arte?
Not really.
Na verdade.
Why do you come to see me? Is there anything I can help?
Por que razão veio ver-me? Posso ajudar em alguma coisa?
If it were told by someone else, I wouldn’t have believed a word.
Se tivesse sido contado por outra pessoa, não teria acreditado em nada.
That all your dreams seem to be connected.
Que todos os seus sonhos parecem estar ligados.
Do you have any idea now that you have seen my sketches?
Agora que já viu os meus esboços, tem alguma ideia?
Archaeology is the study of human past through landscapes, architectures, and other material remain...
A arqueologia é o estudo do passado humano através de paisagens, arquiteturas e outros vestígios materiais...
with traces of culture in the past.
com traços de cultura no passado.
These are, however, what you saw in your dreams.
No entanto, foi isso que viu nos seus sonhos.
I can’t believe they can be connected into a story like this.
Não acredito que possam estar ligados numa história como esta.
But what about the legend about Naga or the fireballs which you can see on every 15th night of the 11th waxing moon?
Mas e a lenda sobre Naga ou as bolas de fogo que se podem ver em cada 15ª noite da 11ª lua crescente?
There are records and traces found that it actually happened, aren’t there?
Há registos e vestígios encontrados de que isso realmente aconteceu, não é?
But those are proves for a living creature which is not human being.
Mas estas são provas de uma criatura viva que não é um ser humano.
It’s just a legend told among the locals.
É apenas uma lenda contada entre os habitantes locais.
Even for the Garuda. There’s hardly any record on this half-human and half-bird creature.
Mesmo para o Garuda. Quase não há registos desta criatura metade humana, metade ave.
Most are just stories found in the religious mythology…
A maioria são apenas histórias encontradas na mitologia religiosa…
which cannot be proofed whether it’s true or not.
que não pode ser provado se é verdadeiro ou não.
So, I’m afraid I can’t help you much with this.
Assim, receio não o poder ajudar muito com isso.
I only say it from my point of view.
Digo-o apenas do meu ponto de vista.
It might actually exist.
Pode até existir.
Like energy forces, souls, or miracles.
Como forças energéticas, almas ou milagres.
They are things that science can’t proof.
São coisas que a ciência não consegue comprovar.
But there are stories told about them.
Mas há histórias contadas sobre eles.
Someone had witnessed those things and record what they saw.
Alguém testemunhou estas coisas e registou o que viu.
Can you tell me where to find more information about it?
Pode dizer-me onde encontrar mais informações sobre isso?
There’s a corner in my gallery where I keep all the records on ancient history.
Há um canto na minha galeria onde guardo todos os registos da história antiga.
You can try looking in that room.
Pode tentar olhar naquela sala.
You might find something useful there.
Pode encontrar algo útil lá.
(Mysterious Sound)
(Som Misterioso)
(The sound of bookshelves shaking)
(O som das estantes a tremer)
King Garuda, why are you here?
Rei Garuda, porque está aqui?
Why did you help me?
Porque é que me ajudou?
You were still alive so I decided to help.
Ainda estavas vivo, então decidi ajudar.
On the 15th day of the 11th month...
No 15º dia do 11º mês...
all the Nagas and Naginis as well as their attendants will present their offerings and breathe out the fireballs as an act of worship.
todos os Nagas e Naginis, bem como os seus assistentes, apresentarão as suas oferendas e exalarão bolas de fogo como ato de adoração.
Beautiful, isn’t it?
Lindo, não é?
Yes.
Sim.
So beautiful.
Tão bonito.
I can’t go with you.
Não posso ir contigo.
I don’t want anyone to die because of me.
Não quero que ninguém morra por minha causa.
Master Sakunanoparuj, this way.
Mestre Sakunanoparuj, por aqui.
Phaya!
Lá!
What happened?
O que aconteceu?
Ouch.
Ai.
I was trying to get the book and the pile just tumbled down.
Estava a tentar pegar no livro e a pilha simplesmente desabou.
Are you all right?
Está bem?
Yeah.
Sim.
I ran here as soon as I heard the noise...
Corri para aqui assim que ouvi o barulho...
and saw you lying unconcious on the floor.
e vi-o deitado inconsciente no chão.
It took quite some time to wake you up. I was so worried.
Demorei um pouco a acordar-te. Fiquei tão preocupada.
I’m so sorry. Your room is a mess now.
Sinto muito. O seu quarto está uma bagunça agora.
- Let me help you tidy up. - It’s all right.
- Deixe-me ajudá-lo a arrumar. - Está tudo bem.
Ouch!
Ai!
(The Son of Naga City Governor)
(O Filho do Governador da Cidade de Naga)
Wi, can I borrow this book for a while?
Wi, podes emprestar-me este livro por um tempo?
Sure.
Claro.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
Oh, hello Doc. Why didn’t you tell me you’d be here today?
Olá, doutor. Porque é que não me avisou que estaria aqui hoje?
My patient just cancelled the appointment.
O meu paciente acabou de cancelar a consulta.
So, I’m thinking maybe we could go out for dinner.
Por isso, estou a pensar que talvez pudéssemos sair para jantar.
Do you want to join me?
Queres juntar-te a mim?
Sure. Please come and wait in my room first.
Claro. Por favor, venha e espere no meu quarto primeiro.
I’ll go get changed.
Vou trocar-me.
Okay.
Ok.
Please come in.
Por favor, entre.
Where are you going?
Onde vai?
He’s going to have dinner with me.
Ele vai jantar comigo.
Do you need anything?
Precisa de alguma coisa?
I’m afraid he can’t go with you now.
Receio que ele não possa ir consigo agora.
Because he’s coming with me.
Porque ele vem comigo.
Come with me, Tharn.
Venha comigo, Tharn.
Hang on.
Espere.
Did I say I’d go with you?
Eu disse que ia contigo?
But I have something important to talk to you.
Mas tenho algo importante para lhe falar.
You have no rights to force him.
Não tem o direito de o forçar.
This is outside of your working hours.
Acontece fora do seu horário de trabalho.
My job is to take care of him.
O meu trabalho é cuidar dele.
But I don’t want to go with you.
Mas eu não quero ir contigo.
Do you remember when I warned you that you might be in danger?
Lembra-se quando eu avisei que poderia estar em perigo?
I told you to stay beside me so that I can protect you.
Eu disse-te para ficares ao meu lado para que eu te possa proteger.
But I’m going with Doc. It’s not dangerous at all.
Mas vou com o Doc. Não é nada perigoso.
Tharn.
Tharn.
If you are really worried about him...
Se está realmente preocupado com ele...
you’d better stay away from him.
é melhor ficar longe dele.
The closer you get to him,
Quanto mais se aproxima dele,
the more danger he’d be in.
maior seria o perigo que ele correria.
The one who actually puts him in danger...
Aquele que realmente o coloca em perigo...
is probably not me. But I think it is.
Provavelmente não sou eu. Mas acho que é.
Since the day you met him, he has to risk his life to save you for so many times.
Desde o dia em que o conheceu, ele teve de arriscar a vida para a salvar inúmeras vezes.
If he were to die,
Se ele morresse,
you’re most likely to be the cause of it.
é bem provável que seja você a causa disso.
What the fuck are you talking about?! Ouch!!
Que porra estás a falar?! Ai!!
Just because he thinks of you as his big brother...
Só porque pensa em si como o seu irmão mais velho...
doesn’t mean that I’d be afraid of you.
não significa que teria medo de ti.
I don’t really give a fuck about anything!
Eu realmente não dou a mínima para nada!
Phaya!
Lá!
You mark my words.
Assinala as minhas palavras.
I will do everything to keep you two apart.
Farei tudo para vos manter os dois separados.
I will take him away from you.
Eu tirá-lo-ei de você.
Even if he has to die.
Mesmo que tenha de morrer.
What the fuck!! (Punching)
Que porcaria é esta!! (Socos)
Are you all right?
Está bem?
Tharn, come with me.
Tharn, venha comigo.
Come with me, Tharn. Let me go! (Punching) Ouch!
Venha comigo, Tharn. Solta-me! (Socos) Ai!
What’s wrong with you?!
O que é que tem?!
Let’s go.
Vamos.
Damn it!
Caramba!
I’m so sorry that he hurt you.
Sinto muito que ele te tenha magoado.
It’s okay. He’s probably very worried about you.
Tudo bem. Provavelmente está muito preocupado consigo.
I don’t know what’s got into him.
Não sei o que lhe deu.
But it makes me want to stay away from him from now on.
Mas faz-me querer ficar longe dele de agora em diante.
This is the floor plan of the art exhibition at the BACC.
Esta é a planta da exposição de arte no BACC.
It’s for the mission that I’ve informed you earlier.
É para a missão que lhe informei anteriormente.
I need a volunteer for this mission.
Preciso de um voluntário para esta missão.
Our job is to protect the important people who would attend the event.
O nosso trabalho é proteger as pessoas importantes que irão comparecer ao evento.
This is a special mission.
Esta é uma missão especial.
It’s not an order from the authority.
Não é uma ordem da autoridade.
That’s why I’m looking for a volunteer.
É por isso que procuro um voluntário.
Raise your hand if you want to volunteer.
Levante a mão se quer ser voluntário.
Are you listening?
Você está a ouvir?
I asked if you were listening.
Perguntei se estava a ouvir.
He asked if you were listening to what he just said.
Perguntou se estavas a ouvir o que ele acabou de dizer.
I didn’t. But I was reading your lips.
Não, não sabia. Mas eu estava a ler os seus lábios.
You want some volunteers to work on a special mission which is not an order from the authority.
Pretende que alguns voluntários trabalhem numa missão especial que não seja uma ordem da autoridade.
Their job is to protect the important people at the exhibition.
O seu trabalho é proteger as pessoas importantes na exposição.
Those who want to volunteer please raise their hands.
Aqueles que quiserem ser voluntários, por favor, levantem a mão.
(Clapping) Wow!
(Aplausos) Uau!
You’re like a bugging device.
Você é como um dispositivo de escuta.
Then I’ll assume everyone already understood what the mission is.
Assim, assumirei que todos já perceberam qual é a missão.
Give me the name list once it’s done.
Dê-me a lista de nomes quando estiver pronta.
I want to do it.
Eu quero fazer isso.
I don’t think it’d be just a simple bodyguard job.
Não creio que seria apenas um simples trabalho de guarda-costas.
I agree.
Concordo.
It’s very strange.
É muito estranho.
Our unit has never taken any job like this before.
A nossa unidade nunca assumiu um trabalho como este antes.
I’m sure there must be something behind this.
Tenho a certeza de que deve haver algo por trás.
We are not allowed to reveal our identity as an IDF officer too.
Também não nos é permitido revelar a nossa identidade como oficiais das FDI.
It’s going to be so interesting.
Vai ser muito interessante.
You get to dress up nicely.
Pode vestir-se bem.
And work at a nice building.
E trabalhar num prédio bonito.
After work, I will keep the suit on and take Sand to dinner at...
Depois do trabalho, ficarei com o fato e levarei a Sand a jantar em...
the food stall in the gas station.
a banca de comida no posto de abastecimento de combustível.
Yeah. And order a spicy minced pork salad with lots of blood.
Sim. E peça uma salada picante de carne de porco picada com muito sangue.
Geez, you eat it yourself then. You got me carried away.
Ui, então coma você mesmo. Deixaste-me louco.
You seem to be in a lovey dovey mode.
Parece estar em estado de amor.
Obviously.
Obviamente.
- Are you in then? - Of course.
- Estás aí então? - Claro.
- Singh, are you in? - Yeah.
- Singh, estás? - Sim.
- If my babe is going then I’ll go too. - (Sigh)
- Se o meu amor vai, eu também vou. - (Suspiro)
Are you going, Mayris?
Vais, Mayris?
No, Inspector probably wants me to find out more information on the Lieutenant Tam’s case.
Não, o inspetor provavelmente quer que eu descubra mais informações sobre o caso do tenente Tam.
Okay.
Ok.
Lieut Tam’s case?
O caso do Tenente Tam?
I thought the authority has ordered to have this case closed.
Pensei que a autoridade tinha ordenado o encerramento deste caso.
They have.
Eles têm.
But the Inspector wants us keep investigating.
Mas o Inspetor quer que continuemos a investigar.
Because Lieut Tam’s body might lead us to the major drug trafficking network backed up by politicians.
Porque o corpo do Tenente Tam pode levar-nos à grande rede de tráfico de droga apoiada por políticos.
Lieut Tam died in the line of duty.
O tenente Tam morreu em serviço.
Huh?
Hã?
You guys didn’t know about this?
Vocês não sabiam disto?
Ahh, you came later.
Ah, veio depois.
Apart from being a coach at our unit,
Além de ser formador na nossa unidade,
Lieut Tam also had another important job in our IDF unit.
O Tenente Tam também tinha outro trabalho importante na nossa unidade das FDI.
He was one of the best spies we’ve ever had.
Foi um dos melhores espiões que já tivemos.
And he was also the Inspector’s right-hand man.
E era também o braço direito do Inspetor.
His mission was to track down the international drug trafficking network...
Tinha como missão rastrear a rede internacional de tráfico de droga...
of which Minister Montree is believed to be the man behind it.
do qual se acredita que o Ministro Montree seja o homem por detrás do mesmo.
Songyod is also one of his minions.
Songyod é também um dos seus asseclas.
He’s actually the Minister’s hand and foot.
Na verdade, ele é a mão e o pé do Ministro.
Then why can’t we just go question Songyod and force him to tell us...
Então porque não podemos simplesmente questionar Songyod e obrigá-lo a dizer-nos...
information that could help destroy Minister Montree’s network?
informação que poderia ajudar a destruir a rede do Ministro Montree?
Our IDF unit’s main job is to investigate.
A principal tarefa da nossa unidade IDF é investigar.
The execution of judgement…
A execução do julgamento…
or determination of punishment is the authority’s job.
ou a determinação da punição é tarefa da autoridade.
- Which we cannot... - We cannot cross the line, right?
- Que não podemos... - Não podemos passar a linha, certo?
Just like many cases in the past that were treated unfairly.
Assim como muitos casos no passado que foram tratados injustamente.
Yeah, including your the case about your parents too.
Sim, incluindo o caso dos seus pais também.
It’s a way to force us to go forward…
É uma forma de nos obrigar a seguir em frente…
but with a rope around our neck.
mas com uma corda à volta do pescoço.
They only allow us to walk in the direction that they are approved of.
Só nos permitem caminhar na direção que aprovam.
Fake freedom, you mean?
Falsa liberdade, quer dizer?
Well then, I won’t be joining you guys this time.
Pois bem, não me vou juntar a vocês desta vez.
I have a more important job to do.
Tenho um trabalho mais importante para fazer.
(Sigh)
(Suspiro)
I’m in.
Estou dentro.
Then go and ask Phaya too.
Por isso, vá e pergunte também à Phaya.
I think he probably wants to join us too.
Acho que ele provavelmente também se quer juntar a nós.
You go and ask him yourself.
Vá você mesmo e pergunte-lhe.
Yai.
Sim.
When did they quarrel?
Quando é que eles brigaram?
Was it at his condo?
Foi no apartamento dele?
Do you really want to know?
Quer mesmo saber?
It’s my job to know about other people’s businesses.
É o meu trabalho saber sobre os negócios de outras pessoas.
Then you go and ask him. I don’t want to mention it.
Então vá e pergunte-lhe. Nem quero mencionar isso.
Geez! You two are the same.
Uau! Vocês os dois são iguais.
I’ll ask baby then.
Então vou perguntar ao bebé.
Baby, Tharn and…
Bebé, Tharn e…
Stop. You’re bothering me. Go away.
Pare. Você está a incomodar-me. Vá-se embora.
- That’s a lot. - Yeah.
- Isso é muito. - Sim.
Inspector never disappoints us. His special mission is so cool.
O Inspetor nunca nos desilude. A missão especial dele é muito gira.
I don’t want to hold a gun tonight.
Não quero segurar uma arma esta noite.
I’d rather hold her instead. Oops!
Prefiro segurá-la. Ops!
If you don’t want to spend a night in a coffin, you’d better quit playing around.
Se não quer passar uma noite num caixão, é melhor parar de brincar.
- Baby. - Good luck.
- Bebé. - Boa sorte.
- I’ll go check on the other side. - Okay.
- Vou verificar do outro lado. - Certo.
If you are mad at him, you should clear it up with him when he comes to work tomorrow.
Se está zangado com ele, deve esclarecer isso com ele quando ele vier trabalhar amanhã.
I don’t have anything to say to him.
Não tenho nada para lhe dizer.
Nothing to say? But your face already said it all.
Nada a dizer? Mas o seu rosto já disse tudo.
He did that because he was worried about you.
Ele fez isso porque estava preocupado consigo.
Hey, Yai. Tharn.
Olá Yai. Tharn.
You guys are here too?
Vocês também estão aqui?
Phaya? What on earth are you doing here?
Phaya? O que está aqui a fazer?
I’m a guest.
Sou um convidado.
This is my grandmother and my little sister.
Esta é a minha avó e a minha irmãzinha.
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Olá. / - Olá.
Inspector has asked our team to help taking care of the security at the event.
O inspetor pediu à nossa equipa que ajudasse a cuidar da segurança do evento.
Excuse me? Are you Tharn?
Com licença? Você é o Tharn?
It’s been a long time since we last met. Do you still remember me?
Já há muito tempo que não nos víamos. Ainda se lembra de mim?
Of course, I do.
Claro que sim.
Phaya only told me that he met a friend who saved his life when he was a kid.
A Phaya só me contou que conheceu um amigo que lhe salvou a vida quando ele era criança.
I didn’t know that you also work at the same unit. The world is round indeed.
Não sabia que também trabalhavam na mesma unidade. O mundo é mesmo redondo.
Well, it might not be because the world is round...
Bem, pode não ser porque o mundo é redondo...
but rather a destiny that brought these two together.
mas sim um destino que uniu estes dois.
Ouch.
Ai.
- Um... / - Ouch.
- Um... / - Ouch.
I can remember your face but not your name.
Lembro-me do seu rosto, mas não do seu nome.
- This is Yai, Grandma. - You’re...
- Esta é a Yai, avó. - Você é...
- Yes. - Another kid at the temple who also saved me that day.
- Sim. - Outra criança no templo que também me salvou nesse dia.
Oh, I see. Now that all of you live in Bangkok, we should see each other more often.
Ah, já percebi. Agora que todos vocês vivem em Banguecoque, devíamos ver-nos com mais frequência.
Please come to my place for a meal whenever you’re free.
Por favor, venha a minha casa para uma refeição sempre que estiver livre.
I’d like to treat you both to a meal as a thank you for saving my grandson.
Gostaria de vos convidar a ambos para uma refeição como agradecimento por terem salvo o meu neto.
Thank you very much, Grandma.
Muito obrigada, avó.
I’m afraid we have to get back to work now.
Receio que tenhamos de voltar ao trabalho agora.
Go on, dear.
Vá em frente, querida.
- Goodbye. / - Goodbye.
- Adeus. / - Adeus.
See you.
Até à próxima.
- Grandma, please wait here for a second. I’ll be right back. - Okay.
- Avó, espere aqui um segundo, por favor. Já volto. - Certo.
Tharn.
Tharn.
Can we talk?
Podemos falar?
You guys talk then.
Então vocês conversam.
You can do it!
Você consegue!
What is it?
O que é?
Well, about that night...
Bem, sobre essa noite...
I’m sorry.
Lamento.
The one you should apologise to is him not me.
A pessoa a quem deve pedir desculpa é a ele, não a mim.
But the one I care about is you.
Mas a pessoa com quem me preocupo é você.
Why do you have to mention him?
Por que razão tem de mencioná-lo?
Phaya.
Lá.
When did you arrive?
Quando chegou?
My aunt is looking for you.
A minha tia está à sua procura.
Where are Grandma and Nee?
Onde estão a avó e a Nee?
Is this your colleague?
Este é o seu colega?
- Hello. / - Hello.
- Olá. / - Olá.
- I’ll go then. / - Hey.
- Eu vou então. / - Ei.
Tharn!
Obrigado!
Grandma and Nee are over there.
A avó e a Nee estão ali.
Please excuse me. I’ll go talk to my colleague first.
Com licença. Vou falar primeiro com o meu colega.
Tharn.
Tharn.
Doc? You’re here too?
Doutor? Também está aqui?
I got invited.
Fui convidado.
It’s an exhibition displaying artworks which reflect on the human’s state of mind.
É uma exposição que exibe obras de arte que refletem o estado de espírito humano.
- Let’s go inside then. - Okay.
- Vamos entrar então. - Certo.
Whom is Phaya talking to?
Com quem está a Phaya a falar?
Is that the girl who came to see him at the unit?
É aquela rapariga que foi vê-lo à unidade?
Doctor Chalothorn.
Doutor Chalothorn.
Yes?
Sim?
Someone wants to see you over there.
Alguém quer vê-lo ali.
Okay.
Ok.
I’m leaving then. I’ll call you after the event.
Vou indo então. Ligo-te depois do evento.
This way, please.
Por aqui, por favor.
Probably just a friend.
Provavelmente apenas um amigo.
He’s still single, isn’t he?
Ele ainda é solteiro, não é?
It has nothing to do with me anyway.
De qualquer forma, não tem nada a ver comigo.
Hmm, are you sure?
Hum, tem a certeza?
Look at your face first.
Olhe primeiro para o seu rosto.
Your face and eyes just say it all.
O seu rosto e os seus olhos dizem tudo.
Tell me honestly,
Diga-me honestamente,
why would you resist your own feelings?
por que razão resistiria aos seus próprios sentimentos?
Love is love.
Amor é amor.
I want to see you happy again, Tharn.
Quero voltar a vê-lo feliz, Tharn.
I want to see you smile like you used to.
Quero ver-te sorrir como antes.
If you’re afraid that loving him would put him in danger,
Se tem medo que amá-lo o coloque em perigo,
I’ll also help you protect him.
Eu também o vou ajudar a protegê-lo.
No need.
Não há necessidade.
I’ll do it because I want to see my brother happy.
Vou fazê-lo porque quero ver o meu irmão feliz.
Got it?
Entendi?
Don’t forget to remind the others to keep an eye on the artworks too.
Não se esqueça de lembrar os outros para também ficarem de olho nas obras de arte.
(Something drops)
(Algo cai)
I’m sorry.
Lamento.
It's OK.
Está tudo bem.
What a pleasure to meet you again, Inspector.
Que prazer voltar a conhecê-lo, Inspetor.
Hello, Mr. Montree.
Olá, Sr. Montree.
Have we met before? You look so familiar.
Já nos conhecemos? Pareces tão familiar.
Let me remind you again that your job today...
Deixe-me voltar a lembrá-lo que o seu trabalho hoje...
is to protect the safety of important guests who attend the event.
é proteger a segurança dos convidados importantes que assistem ao evento.
Arghhhh!!!
Arghhh!!!
Love doesn’t exist. They are all lies.
O amor não existe. São tudo mentiras.
You must pay for what you did.
Deve pagar pelo que fez.
🎵I will always cherish this love in my heart.🎵
🎵Guardarei sempre este amor no meu coração.🎵
🎵No matter for how long, I’ll always want to see you.🎵
🎵Não importa por quanto tempo, vou sempre querer ver-te.🎵
🎵I want you to know that you are the one that I want.🎵
🎵Quero que saibas que és a pessoa que eu quero.🎵
🎵I’m going to love you and only you.🎵
🎵Eu vou amar-te e só a ti.🎵
🎵No matter for how lond, it will never change.🎵
🎵Não importa por quanto tempo, isso nunca mudará.🎵
🎵Whether in my sleep or while I’m awake.🎵
🎵Seja a dormir ou acordado.🎵
🎵I’ll never forget you.🎵
🎵Nunca te esquecerei.🎵
🎵No matter for how long, I’ll always love you.🎵
🎵Não importa por quanto tempo, amar-te-ei sempre.🎵
🎵Love you with all my heart.🎵
🎵Amo-te com todo o meu coração.🎵
🎵No one can take your place because my heart belongs to you.🎵
🎵Ninguém pode ocupar o teu lugar porque o meu coração pertence-te.🎵